

HEIN HTET SOE MOE

DEVELOPER BUSINESS ANALYST

CONTACT

+959 799 827 807



heinhtet2127@gmail.com



21 st street, Latha, Yangon



heinhtetsoemoe.herokuapp.com

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Error Handling
- Client Communication
- Clickup, Hubspot, Figma

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- · former assistant lecturer of The Myanmar Dream web development classes
- Team member of Donation For Yangon and also volunteered in multiple nonprofit organizations

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Laravel

Wordpress

React

Javascript

.....

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Creative and people-oriented computer scientist with up to 2 years of working with tech startups. Advanced knowledge of software design principles and agile development principles. Strong understanding of digital transformation. A good negotiator of dealing with multiple client complains. Passionate youth, looking for challenges

EDUCATION

Dual diploma in computing (programming)

KBTC University (2020-2022)

Level 5 diploma in computing

NCC Education (2020-2022)

WORK EXPERIENCES

Dinger

Developer & Business Analyst | May 2022 - Present Junior Web Developer | Aug 2020 to April 2022

- · Developing new websites, maintaining present websites and support for upcoming new features
- As an Business Analyst, deals with client's technical errors and looking for new potential clients

Lastoenjoy (web development agency)

Senior Frontend Developer | Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

• Developing client projects, work closely with customer support, design team and deal with APIs

Tech T-Rex

Founder & CEO | June 2022 - present

· Serves for web development ,SEO optimization and hosting services

Bards

Junior Web Developer | Aug 2020 to April 2022

 Assists as junior website developer and helped in developing multiple client websites

(Dinger is the product of Bards.LTD)